# DMITRY NASANOVICH

PYTHON DEVELOPER

+380677702977 🕲 s7octav@gmail.com 🗟

github.com/s7octav ( )
Odessa Ukraina ( )

# **PROFILE**



I have actively been learning python for 9 months. I have passed a stepik course and have received a certificate. I have no commercial experience. However, I have made several projects on writing telegram bots. During the writing projects, I encountered Database & SQL, FTP, SSH, Docker. I can host and configure projects on VDS, Unix / Linux systems. Working with asynchronous programming a syncio, aiogram, webhook, os, Git, environment variables and other. Having also a basic knowledge of HTML & CSS, where I administered my website.

### **EXPERIENCE**

#### 2020 - 2022 Mining BTC.com

Connection and service. Installing software, monitoring the performance and correct operation of the equipment. Periodic maintenance of hash boards.

#### 2016 - 2020 VOIP

Termination of telephone traffic from the network to the cells of the mobile operator. Installation of specialized software and hardware. Control of the correct operation and quality sound transmission.

#### 2014 - 2016 Sales Technician

Advising customers on the properties, quality and service of goods. Sold various goods, such as: TVs, cell phones, laptops, cameras, small appliances

MY SKILLS		LANGUAGES
<del></del>		
Python	Photoshop	English
Unix / Linux	HTML/CSS -	Italian <b>——</b>
FTP & SSH	Database / SQL	Ukrainian
Docker	VPN & VDS	Russian

## **EDUCATION**

2021 - 2022 Generation Python : beginner course Generation Python : advanced course

1997 - 2001 Manager Secondary special education College of Commerce and Enterprise

- I took a course with practice at stepik.org and received a certificate. Actually, I practice an advanced course where I have been studying it for 9 months.
- College of retail and wholesale trade. I have studied for 4 years. Leading subjects: marketing, economics, management